My man right here is in the RA.
We're going to go see if we
can get a quick interview with him.
Hey, quick question for you, bro.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
About a million dollars.
Today, we're going to be asking
Texan millionaires how they got rich
and how you can start your
path to becoming wealthy in today's world.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Over half a million dollars.
In what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I've done a couple of things.
I've actually been a wealth manager.
I've been president and CEO of a company before.
And I've also have my own construction company.
What was the biggest thing
that you implemented throughout your companies
to ultimately scale your businesses?
To scale a business, you got to crawl, walk, run.
You don't want to go out there
and go all out right from the start
because you've got to be
able to pick yourself back up.
And if you're running too
fast, you'll probably over leverage yourself.
You'll go into debt too much, learn
the industry and become an expert in it.
What was the best financial decision
that you ever made throughout your career?
Getting married to this young lady right here.
You got to have a happy and good
personal life to be successful in your business life.
If it's all about business, at the
end of the road, you won't be happy.
What is the best piece of
advice that you would tell your young
yourself?
That every day is an interview.
Every day is your resume.
It's not what you do when you speak
to somebody for 30 minutes in a conversation.
It's everything that you do every day
and how you live your life, your attitude,
how you behave.
Basically, an effect that allows you
to address any questions or any circumstance
you could have at any company
or any individual during the interview process.
Your quick intermission.
He's going to be drawing
a caricature of us real quick.
He's got Josh here on the stool.
We'll be checking back in with him
just to see how the drawing's going.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Bioinformatics.
Computer science and medical school combined.
Yeah.
So are you a business owner?
I actually just sold my business a few months ago.
How much did you sell it for?
I'm not at liberty to disclose, but I did okay.
As an entrepreneur, what advice would you tell
to someone starting a business in today's world?
I would say that perseverance is one
of the most underappreciated aspects of a business.
It's this idea that in spite of everything,
if it looks like things are going to fail,
to stick with it and believe in yourself
and your team's ability to overcome the adversity
that's going to come your way.
Everybody experiences friction.
Growth only comes from that.
And the people that make it
are the ones that make it.
And the ones that stick with it and just
find a way in spite of all the odds.
What do you think is the best industry that
people should be looking to get into in today's world?
It's in AI.
There's huge advancements right now with
chat, chat, GTP and other things.
This is just the beginning.
Your job won't be replaced by an AI.
Your job will be replaced by someone who
knows how to use AI for their job.
Just wrapped up some interviews down at the Riverwalk.
We're here at the Westin on
the Riverwalk down in San Antonio.
Going to go in real quick and see if
we can snag a couple interviews inside the hotel.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
About a million dollars.
That's amazing.
What's your net worth?
About 15 to 20 million.
When someone is starting to make money in their careers,
where do you think people should really look to
invest or put their money to try and multiply
and grow the income that they do have?
Well, in real estate, I would say right
now in land, they're not making any more.
And the land development right
now, the costs are always increasing.
And you can always do something with the land.
If you buy something that has
what they call an agricultural use,
you're not paying very much in taxes.
Eventually, when you sell it and develop it,
you'll get your return and your
capital gains will come out of there.
What's the greatest lesson that you've learned?
Throughout your career as a real estate developer?
Don't be afraid.
Take the plunge.
You'll always come up ahead if you take the risk.
No matter if you fail,
you'll always come ahead of yourself
because you'll learn something from your failure.
We're going to go check
back in with Josh and Blas
and see how the character drawing is going right now.
So how long have you been
drawing and doing character shows for?
For about 35 years.
Oh my God, that's incredible.
Yeah.
What is the most fascinating thing
you've learned about people since drawing?
People from all over are friendly.
And, you know, most people are nice and generous.
And everybody's excited.
And they all want to know what
they would look like in a caricature form.
So I'm really grateful.
And I feel very blessed to be here
on the Riverwalk and drawing you guys especially.
Why did you choose to go into
art and drawing people for a living?
I wanted to be like Picasso.
That was my whole idea.
When I was younger, I thought,
geez, I'm going to be famous like Picasso.
I love Picasso.
He's a great guy.
And he seems like a likable guy and everything else.
So I never got it that far.
But here I am.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
I'm in the like $300,000 to $400,000 range.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I'm an architect.
Are you a business owner by any chance?
Yep.
I own my own business.
I work for myself, by myself.
What's the business?
Katie Hastings Architecture.
What is your best financial advice
that you would tell to the younger generation
that you wish someone told you
when you were coming out of school?
Seek out your own destiny.
There's many different jobs with many different incomes.
You have to make choices based on
the lifestyle that you want to live.
All right, guys.
Blast is finishing up right now with Jocelyn.
We're going to go see how the drawing is ending.
What would you say is the best piece of advice
that you'd give to the younger generation?
Oh, just it's so important nowadays to believe in yourself
and not just believe in yourself, but
continue, you know, just never give up.
Because, I mean, I've been
doing this for a long time
and it took a lot to
actually be at the level I'm at.
I've drawn almost half a million people,
not realizing that I was going
to draw half a million people.
And I never gave up.
I never, I've always believed in myself.
And it's very important.
Just never give up and keep moving.
And you'll get there eventually.
My man right here is in the RA.
We're going to go see if we
can get a quick interview with him.
Hey, quick question for you, bro.
If you were to go back to when
you were in either high school or college
and you're having a conversation with your younger self,
what is the best piece of
advice you'd tell your younger self?
I would say stay consistent 24-7.
Because as you get older,
things that get in your life,
it's a discipline and just being consistent, man.
And you can make it anywhere.
I think I noticed you guys
from the School of Hard Knocks.
So I appreciate y'all, man.
Yes, sir.
And I live right here, man.
So y'all want to check out the spot.
Is that cool if we come up?
Yeah, that's cool.
Let's get it, bro.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Real estate was the first
big thing that I invested in.
What's the most amount of money that
you ever made in a single year?
Probably 1.3 I did gross total.
You know, how can someone really start
their path to becoming wealthy in today's world?
Finding something that you're
really, really passionate about first.
Because when you're passionate about it,
you typically go pretty hard and then invest in it,
learn everything around it.
And then from there, duplicate
that same deal every single time.
Just take one platform and you just multiply that.
How many units or how many pieces
of property do you own right now?
Units and properties together, about 38, 40.
What is the biggest mindset change that
is needed in order to become a multimillionaire?
I would say staying humble.
Staying humble is a very, very key to growth.
With the humbleness, you never stop learning.
I think being open and staying humble is like,
the key that I would give a
lot of people because there's endless growth.
How did you get started doing Airbnb?
It was a friend of mine that
I saw on the internet, on YouTube.
I reached out to him and
he kind of gave me some pointers.
I actually did a training, fitness training as
an exchange instead of actually paying for the service.
And then that's kind of how I got started.
And then I met a lot
of other people along the way.
I got into another program with
Sean, which is Airbnb Automated on YouTube.
So I learned a lot from everybody.
For you to go back to when you started
getting into real estate and getting that initial knowledge,
but you had zero property, zero rentals right now,
what would be that first step you
would take to acquire that first deal?
Definitely research.
I would research a whole lot.
You know, go to certain websites, go to Airbnb itself.
Look at the city that you're
looking at and look at the area.
Try to find something around that area,
whether you're buying it or you're going to
overcharge whatever it is and just dive into it.
Then, I mean, I was fortunate to
get to where I'm at with the properties,
but I did do a little research, but I would have
done more if I would have known what I know now.
Someone's just looking to get into that first property.
How much could they expect to try to be
able to make them that in
a year off of one property?
Gross.
I mean, it can be anywhere
from 3000 to 5500 a month.
I have houses that do 80,
85 a month, but those are houses.
So it just depends on what you're offering, how
big the house is, how small the unit is.
We're here with the RA.
You have an exotic car rental business.
How did you get started in that?
So I got started mainly with the properties and
it's kind of like an enterprise in a way.
They're booking a property as like a hotel.
So then they need vehicles, they need transportation.
So I offer regular vehicles and
then I started getting exotic vehicles.
So I just give the best experience possible.
And that's where the cars come into play.
So if someone wanted to rent
from you, how does that process work?
Like, do you drive the vehicle to them?
Do they come pick it up?
Most of them will come pick it up.
But I mean, it's through Turo.
So Turo is just like the Airbnb for cars.
So once you have that, it's a very smooth process.
What cars do you currently
have in your fleet right now?
Three series BMW have an i8
on the supercar, not supercar side,
but the i8 on the supercar side.
So what cars do you currently
have in your fleet right now?
The exotic side, GT Mercedes,
which is on the supercar exotic,
the RA, which is on a supercar exotic.
I have a few other
like Toyotas and things like that.
E400 as well, Mercedes.
That's about it right now.
About six cars in the fleet.
So how much could you make off
of, let's say, a rental for the RA?
A month, you can make about eight to
ten grand a month on some of the cars,
if not more.
RA typically goes for about six, seven hundred a day,
depending on how long the person books it.
But it's booked every weekend, just about.
It's not booked right now because I need,
I want to drive it.
Yeah, I think that's the coolest
thing about the exotic car business is
you get to rent it
out, make some profit on it,
and you get the pleasure of driving it.
So if someone wanted to get
started in the exotic car rental business,
how would you recommend them get started?
Get your LLC going, learn how
to get the vehicles in your LLC.
You might have to build up some business credit,
but some like Mercedes will allow you
to get in without having the business credit.
It's also going to be based on
how much you kind of make, too.
When it comes down to the
down payment, you can grow really fast.
Actually, in the exotic, if that's
like your go to for me,
it was just something to be another
layer on top of something else already.
Guys, that wraps up today's video.
Thank you so much for tuning in.
If you guys enjoyed, make
sure that you leave a like
and subscribe for tons of amazing content on the way.
And if you guys want to see video
of us going around to the wealthiest golf
courses to ask millionaires how they got
rich, click the link to watch the video
right now.